Nilesh Sahebrao Badgujar

Contact: +91 9922469122 E-mail: *nileshbadgujar7@gmail.com* Pimpri Kh, Tal: Dharangaon, Dist.: Jalgaon-425104

PROFILE

Sincere & diligent qualified with BSC (CS) offering over 11 years of experience in Computer Science environment. Currently spearheading efforts with Softaid Computers Pvt. Ltd. as Software Developer. Exposure to complete Database and Implementation of major systems and accented with the latest trends and techniques of the field.

Possess working knowledge on various tools, technologies like **ASP.NET MVC and MS SQL Server**. Acquire good knowledge of **Database Handling, Coding, Unit testing and Maintenance**. Analytical thinker, consistently resolving ongoing issues, often called upon to consult on problems that have eluded resolution by others.

KEY SKILLS

Languages C#, HTML, LINQ, JQuery. **Technologies** ASP.NET MVC, Bootstrap.

Databases MS SQL Server 2008 / 12 / 14 / 16 / 17.

Frameworks .NET 4.0 /4.5 /4.7.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

RISHI COMPUTERS PVT.LTD.JALGAON • Technical Support Engineer

• Since Feb 2011 - December 2013 (2.10 Years)

IL&FS EDUCATION & SERVICES LTD. • Technical Support Engineer

• Since December 2013 – July 2017(4.7 Years)

SOFTAID COMPUTERS PVT. LTD., JALGAON • Software Developer

• Since July 2017 - Till Date (4.3 Years)

- Providing direct support, development and designing of the software applications and integrations for development functions related to complex applications and software programs.
- Assuring quality & customer service, leading & driving advanced/complex development projects to implementation.
- Ensuring technical solutions are designed for performance, reliability, scalability, maintainability, supportability, business continuity, and business agility while leveraging industry's best practices
- Gaining exposure in end-to-end development of software products from requirement analysis to system study and designing.

PROJECTS UNDERTAKEN ACROSS CAREER PATH

1. Title	Soft Campus

Technologies ASP.NET MVC, JQuery and MS SQL Server 2017

Responsibilities Requirement Gathering, Designing, Implementation, Database and Client Support. **Description** Admission System from Student Applications to final Confirmation including

Admission System from Student Applications to final Confirmation including

Admission System, Fees Module, Exam Form And Hall Ticket, Exam Module and Result Generation, Library Management Module, Stock Inventory Module And so on.

Responsibilities Requirement Gathering, Designing, Implementation and Support.

2. Title Hospital Management System

Technologies ASP.NET MVC, JQuery and MS SQL Server.

Responsibilities Requirement Gathering, Designing, Implementation Database and Client Support. **Description** Patient Registration to final Confirmation, OPD and IPD Module, Bill Generation and

so on.

3. Title Soft Campus App (Parent, Teacher and Management)

Technologies Web API (.NET MVC) and MS SQL Server

Responsibilities Requirement Gathering, Designing, Implementation, Database and Client Support. **Description** Homework management along with submission by student and approval by

Homework management along with submission by student and approval by Management/Staff, Circular Module with approval by Management, Messaging

Module along with 3 layer communication, MCQ exam complete module, Files Upload,

Time Table and So on.

4. Title MIS System Development

Technologies Web API (.NET MVC) and MS SQL Server

Responsibilities Requirement Gathering, Designing, Implementation, Database and Client Support. **Description** Staff Attendance Module, Client Visit Module along with marketing visits tracking.

Visit Expense Management, Client Requirements Management, Client Location Setting, App Offers the surest way to track employees attendance wherever, whenever you want, No to Buddy Punching! Keep a check on employee Time &

Location with high accuracy.

5. Title Employee Attendance and Payroll App.

Technologies Web API (.NET MVC) and MS SQL Server

Responsibilities Requirement Gathering, Designing, Implementation, Database and Client Support. **Description** Office Location Setting, Attendance Module, Visit Management, Employee Leave

Office Location Setting, Attendance Module, Visit Management, Employee Leave Application, Leave Approval by management, Location Tracking, All Reports

(Attendance, Visit Leave), App Offers the surest way to track employees attendance wherever, whenever you want, No to Buddy Punching! Keep a check on employee

Time & Location with high accuracy.

6. Title SoftCore Banking Software.

Technologies ASP.NET MVC Web, JQuery and MS SQL Server 2017

Responsibilities Requirement Gathering, Designing, Implementation, Database and Client Support.

Description Customer Master, Account Master having different types of heads, Share Holder

Entry, Interest Calculations, All Borrowing Indexing Reports and so on.

Responsibilities Requirement Gathering, Designing, Implementation and Support.

EDUCATIONAL CREDENTIALS

B.Sc(CS)	North Maharashtra University	72.25%
H.S.C	Maharashtra State Board	63.18%
S.S.C	Maharashtra State Board	77.20%.

EXTRA-CURRUCULAR ACCOLADES

- Passed ONCET for MS-CIT Learning Facilitators Exam with 81%.
- Passed Installation Technician-Computing and Peripherals examination conducted by Telecom Sector Skill Council under the Scheme Skill Development in ESDM for Digital India of Dept. of Electronics & Information Technology (Deity).
- Passed UIDAI Examination for Aadhar Enrollment with Grade EA_SUPERVISOR.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date Of Birth21st Jan 1989PAN Card No.BLNPB915CAadhar Card No.481737812205

Linguistic Proficiency English, Hindi and Marathi. **References** Available On Request.